JOÃO MARTINS

PROGRAMMER & 3D ARTIST



- +351 913686726
- ✓ joaocmrtns@gmail.com
- Mafamude V. N. Gaia
- jmartins.artstation.com
- **IEFP ID:** 7866504

SKILLS

- 3D Modeling
- Programming in C#, C and Java
- Problem-Solving
- Creative

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF GAMES AND MULTIMEDIA

Instituto Politécnico de Leiria 2020-2023

INFORMATION SYSTEMS AND PROGRAMMING TECHNICIAN

IEFP Instituto de Emprego e Formação Profissional

2023 - Ongoing

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English

PROFILE

I am a programmer and 3D artist with three years of experience in game development and asset creation. Strong attention to detail and creative skills. I am looking to improve my Programming capabilities and professional workflow.

EXPERIENCE

GAME PROGRAMMER AND ARTIST

Worldskills Portugal Norte

May 2024 - Ongoing

 Participant of the 2024 Worldskills Portugal Norte in the game development sector

3D ARTIST AND SOUND DESIGNER

Ars Ludendi Studio | Magno Capite

March 2023 - September 2023

- Development of game-ready 3D models in Blender
- Sound design and production using foley and sound editing software

2D AND 3D ARTIST

Lost Bacon Studios | FAXED

2022

- Creation of concept art and UI elements
- 3D modeling and implementation of game assets, including character rigging and animations, using Autodesk Maya

GAME PROGRAMMER

Cloverly Studios | Brave Little Bird

2021

- Game development on the Unity game engine
- Programming in C#

JOÃO MARTINS

PROGRAMADOR E ARTISTA 3D



- +351 913686726
- ✓ joaocmrtns@gmail.com
- Mafamude V. N. Gaia
- jmartins.artstation.com
- ID IEFP: 7866504

PERFIL

Sou programador e artista 3D com 3 anos de experiência em desenvolvimento de jogos e criação de assets. Grande atenção a detalhes e habilidades criativas. Procuro melhorar as minhas capacidades de programação assim como o meu workflow profissional.

APTIDÕES

- Modelação 3D
- Programação em C#, C e Java
- Resolução de problemas
- Criativo

EDUCAÇÃO

LICENCIADO EM JOGOS DIGITAIS E MULTIMÉDIA

Instituto Politécnico de Leiria 2020-2023

FORMAÇÃO - TÉCNICO ESPECIALISTA EM SISTEMAS DE INFORMAÇÃO E PROGRAMAÇÃO

IEFP Instituto de Emprego e Formação Profissional

2023 - Em curso

IDIOMAS

- Português
- Inglês

EXPERIÊNCIA

PROGRAMADOR E ARTISTA DE JOGO

Worldskills Portugal Norte

Maio 2024 - Em curso

 Participante do Worldskills Portugal Norte na área de desenvolvimento de jogos digitais

ARTISTA 3D E DESIGNER DE SOM

Ars Ludendi Studio | Magno Capite

Março 2023 - Setembro 2023

- Desenvolvimento de modelos 3D prontos para jogo no Blender
- Design e produção de sons usando foley e software de edição de som

ARTISTA DE JOGO

Lost Bacon Studios | FAXED

2022

- Criação de concept art e de elementos de UI
- Modelação 3D e implementação de assets de jogo, incluindo rigging de personagens e animações utilizando o Autodesk Maya

PROGRAMADOR DE JOGO

Cloverly Studios | Brave Little Bird

2021

- Desenvolvimento de jogo no motor de jogos Unity
- Programação em C#